{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "a fly\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "flies",
      "explain": "\n\n- fly -> flies\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bike\n\n---> five ___",
      "answer": "bikes",
      "explain": "\n\n- bike -> bikes",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a motto\n\n---> three ____",
      "answer": "mottoes",
      "explain": "\n\n- motto -> mottoes\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a consonant -> +es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a house \n\n---> six ___ ",
      "answer": "houses",
      "explain": "\n\n- house -> houses",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cherry\n\n---> five ___",
      "answer": "cherries",
      "explain": "\n\n- cherry -> cherries\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a clock \n\n---> eight ___ ",
      "answer": "clocks",
      "explain": "\n\n- clock -> clocks",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a child \n\n---> three  ___ ",
      "answer": "children",
      "explain": "\n\n- child -> children\n(irregular plural)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hero\n\n---> six ___",
      "answer": "heroes",
      "explain": "\n\n- hero -> heroes\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a consonant -> +es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a rose\n\n---> nine ___",
      "answer": "roses",
      "explain": "\n\n- rose -> roses",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a knife\n\n---> seven ___",
      "answer": "knives",
      "explain": "\n\n- knife -> knives\nSome nouns ending in f or fe -> changing f or fe to - ves. ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "4"
    }
  ]
}